好的，好的，我今天成为第一个发表演讲的人
okay okay I become the first person to give presentation today hello everyone
give presentation today hello everyone my name is Tina I'm the first year
我叫蒂娜（Tina）我是该系第一年的研究生
my name is Tina I'm the first year graduate student in the department
graduate student in the department working with environmental combustion
与环境燃烧一起工作是被摧毁，我是实验人员
working with environmental combustion yes destroyed I'm experimental people
yes destroyed I'm experimental people and majority of my previous research and
我以前的大部分研究和正在进行的工作都与实验有关
and majority of my previous research and ongoing job are related to experiment
ongoing job are related to experiment instead of computation so this causes
而不是计算，因此这是我有史以来最具挑战性的课程
instead of computation so this causes the most challenging class I've ever
the most challenging class I've ever taken but do I have to do I'm very
采取，但我必须要做的事我对此非常感兴趣，我们肯定
taken but do I have to do I'm very interested in that and we definitely
interested in that and we definitely know a lot although sometimes we are
知道很多，尽管有时我们是他们承受压力，并为我的礼物
know a lot although sometimes we are they take pressure and for my present
they take pressure and for my present for my future I just like a candle is
为了我的未来，我就像蜡烛一样，如果您想尝试这个话题，
for my future I just like a candle is the topic which I want to try if you
the topic which I want to try if you want to apply what we've learned class
希望将我们所学的课程应用于使用
want to apply what we've learned class to a real world case which is using the
to a real world case which is using the Bayesian network approaches to predict
贝叶斯网络方法预测井场火灾后果
Bayesian network approaches to predict the well fire consequence
the well fire consequence well fire we generate some some damage
好火，我们会产生一些损害，如果您
well fire we generate some some damage and you lead to some cost if you are
and you lead to some cost if you are person working maybe government
你有井喷时，可能是政府部门的工作人员
person working maybe government department when there is a well fire you
department when there is a well fire you will be probably surrounded by a lot of
可能会被很多来自不同媒体的人包围着
will be probably surrounded by a lot of people from different media keep asking
people from different media keep asking you unknowing questions about the
您不知道有关井火后果的问题吗？
you unknowing questions about the consequence of the well fire do you want
consequence of the well fire do you want to be complete - good job you have to
要完整-好工作，你必须让他们失望
to be complete - good job you have to keep them down raise doubt the the
keep them down raise doubt the the consequence of the world fire however a
世界大火的后果，但真正的价值是福利的核算
consequence of the world fire however a true value is accountant of the welfare
true value is accountant of the welfare it's kind of hard job because it's
这是一项艰苦的工作，因为它是来自许多不同领域的信息
it's kind of hard job because it's information from many different areas
information from many different areas for example you have to think about the
例如，您必须考虑城市的类型和道路
for example you have to think about the type of your city and you the road
type of your city and you the road density and your type of your
密度和建筑类型这是一种知识
density and your type of your construction it's a kind of knowledge
construction it's a kind of knowledge from stable engineering and the
与稳定的工程和景观环境有关
from stable engineering and the landscape environment something related
landscape environment something related to geology or biology and the value of
地质或生物学以及建筑物的价值
to geology or biology and the value of your building
your building finish their job of Business School so
完成商学院的工作，所以您的话语复杂而艰巨，而且一直保持下去
finish their job of Business School so your word complex and hard and it keeps
your word complex and hard and it keeps the nightmares who the traditional
传统上我自己来计算计数任务的噩梦
the nightmares who the traditional myself to calculate the counts quest
myself to calculate the counts quest however the Bayesian network or hurdle
但是，贝叶斯网络或障碍可以取决于来自
however the Bayesian network or hurdle can depend on the information from
can depend on the information from different area very well as same time
很好地同时在不同的区域，并且有很多研究人员在使用
different area very well as same time and there are many researchers using
and there are many researchers using Bayesian network to do some work on
贝叶斯网络在不同领域做一些工作，例如生物学
Bayesian network to do some work on different areas for example the biology
different areas for example the biology system and you know well fire and this
系统，你知道火，这个人叫我，我不知道他
system and you know well fire and this person whose name is I don't know his
person whose name is I don't know his name the correct pronunciation he
命名他发展互联网工作的正确发音，然后用户
name the correct pronunciation he develop up internet work and the user to
develop up internet work and the user to access the suicide the building damage
获得自杀的建筑损失称为买井火的费用。
access the suicide the building damage called the cost to buy well fire in
called the cost to buy well fire in tableau and in his work he just used use
tableau，在他的工作中，他只是使用了名为
tableau and in his work he just used use the software commercial software named
the software commercial software named fusion mister very strong software you
融合雾化器非常强大的软件，您无法或实际上会破坏贝叶斯
fusion mister very strong software you can't or actually tore your Bayesian
can't or actually tore your Bayesian network and that's the input your CPT
网络，这就是您的CPT的输入，然后点击运行，您将获得
network and that's the input your CPT and click run and you will get your
and click run and you will get your result not very simple but he might I'm
结果不是很简单，但是他可能会担心他对工作的兴趣并想要
result not very simple but he might I'm worried the interest in his job and want
worried the interest in his job and want to want to reproduce his work to a
想将他的作品复制为类似作品，但我不想使用
to want to reproduce his work to a similar work but I don't want to use
similar work but I don't want to use commercial software and I want to use
商业软件，我想使用它来查看网络中如此繁忙的网络
commercial software and I want to use that want to view so busy a network in
that want to view so busy a network in MATLAB and to select several inference
MATLAB并选择几个推理引擎，然后尝试看看我能得到什么
MATLAB and to select several inference engines and try to see what I can get to
engines and try to see what I can get to decide or a silent
决定或无声极限理论，看并且很大
decide or a silent limit theory and see and is very large
limit theory and see and is very large and the wire here for you to study the
和电线在这里供您研究整个岛，我花了时间和时间
and the wire here for you to study the whole island I spend time and to as
whole island I spend time and to as is also similar in my work we just
在我的工作中也很相似我们只是将这个岛分成几个部分
is also similar in my work we just separate this island into several into
separate this island into several into thousands of a hotel and so each time we
成千上万的酒店，因此每次我们只关注一个线单元
thousands of a hotel and so each time we just the focus on one wire cells which
just the focus on one wire cells which is represented by the right square in
由该事件中的右方表示，并且具有血液
is represented by the right square in the in the matter and it has blood has
the in the matter and it has blood has the area of one of one kilometer square
现在，我们决定将目标确定为1公里见方之一的面积
the area of one of one kilometer square now we decided our aim just tells the
now we decided our aim just tells the next step we try to figure out one way
下一步，我们尝试找出一种量化井的所有后果的方法
next step we try to figure out one way to quantify all the consequences of well
to quantify all the consequences of well fire several researchers has established
几位研究人员建立了这个常数，表明该常数
fire several researchers has established this constants which indicate that the a
this constants which indicate that the a good way to formular the expected value
制定井眼火势期望值的好方法是此函数
good way to formular the expected value of the of the well fire is this function
of the of the well fire is this function and this one lifetime size expected
而这个一生的大小期望值可能是小值而离开
and this one lifetime size expected value may be the little value and leave
value may be the little value and leave the function of probability of hazard
危险概率和破坏概率的函数
the function of probability of hazard and the probability of damage
and the probability of damage conditional hazard and here and fiercely
有条件的危害，这里还有剧烈的成本函数，所以上周末我们
conditional hazard and here and fiercely cost function and so last weekend we
cost function and so last weekend we know this formula we've got some hint to
知道这个公式，我们有一些提示可以考虑考虑指标以
know this formula we've got some hint to to think to consider the indicator to to
to think to consider the indicator to to consider the the way to comic-con
考虑漫画计算的方式是下一个结果
consider the the way to comic-con calculates are a consequence the next
calculates are a consequence the next that we tried to find indicator
我们试图找到指标代表损坏等，让我们
that we tried to find indicator represent either the damage etc let's
represent either the damage etc let's come back to the little cells again and
再次回到小牢房，现在没有叔叔也没有法官
come back to the little cells again and no judge nor no no are now uncle in job
no judge nor no no are now uncle in job is to find the indicators even if in the
是要找到指标，即使在小单元格中它们仍然很多
is to find the indicators even if in the little cell they are still a lot of
little cell they are still a lot of indicator you have to think about for
您必须考虑的指标，例如，我们假设帽商是
indicator you have to think about for example we assume that the Hatters to be
example we assume that the Hatters to be the burn area and fire intensity and
燃烧面积和火烈度为零和大地
the burn area and fire intensity and zero several and the earth
zero several and the earth something influenced your damage maybe
某些因素可能会影响您的损坏，例如您的建筑物类型，如果
something influenced your damage maybe for example your your building type if
for example your your building type if it is the apartment or it's a single
它是公寓，还是一栋建筑物，其中有多少栋建筑物
it is the apartment or it's a single building and the how many building in
building and the how many building in this location the building density and
此位置的建筑密度，同时您与火之间的距离
this location the building density and at same times your distance to the fire
at same times your distance to the fire station and the road surround you
车站和道路周围，也许您也可能在
station and the road surround you maybe maybe also maybe play a role in
maybe maybe also maybe play a role in strife because love did not decide that
之所以发生冲突，是因为爱情并不能决定您有机会从大火中获得帮助
strife because love did not decide that your chance to get help from fire
your chance to get help from fire department if you have a better chance
部门，如果您有更好的机会找到控制财富的机会
department if you have a better chance to find a chance to control the wealth
to find a chance to control the wealth but also fire not will definitely reduce
但也不会因火灾而降低您的成本
but also fire not will definitely reduce your cost
your cost so this speaker just gave me something
所以这位演讲者给了我一些东西，使我们对如何融合
so this speaker just gave me something give us some hint about how to fuse the
give us some hint about how to fuse the classic model so what watch the
经典模型，那么我们可以创建什么样的指标来研究
classic model so what watch the indicator we want to study we can create
indicator we want to study we can create these weak raises to act involve graphic
这些微不足道的举动涉及像这样的图形模型，说实话
these weak raises to act involve graphic model like this and to be honest the
model like this and to be honest the several indicator has been already
几个指标已经被忽略了我们只想研究的意义
several indicator has been already ignored sense we only want to study
ignored sense we only want to study something we are really really
我们真的很感兴趣，这对您来说很难
something we are really really interested and it's very hard for you to
interested and it's very hard for you to study piracy in the to build everything
研究盗版，将所有内容装在瓶子中，放在顶部
study piracy in the to build everything in a bottle and on the top the while
in a bottle and on the top the while each node represents the the hazard
每个节点都代表着着火和着火的危险
each node represents the the hazard which is the burn area and fire
which is the burn area and fire intensity so little at least a light
强度如此之小，至少代表该项目的浅绿色节点位于
intensity so little at least a light green nodes representing the item at at
green nodes representing the item at at the item at risk with this list we call
该列表中处于风险中的物品，我们称之为资源管理器
the item at risk with this list we call it Explorer this knows where you cost
it Explorer this knows where you cost your damage after your building and you
您在建筑物建造后所遭受的损失以及您的主要损失，因此除非我们处理了
your damage after your building and you their major cost so unless we get to our
their major cost so unless we get to our model the next stop is to connect up to
建立下一站的模型是连接起来以找到条件概率
model the next stop is to connect up to find the conditional probability
find the conditional probability distribution and and here we do another
分布，在这里我们做另一个假设，我们假设每个
distribution and and here we do another another assumption that we assume each
another assumption that we assume each node has finite state and and we assume
节点具有有限状态，并且我们还假设北跟随
node has finite state and and we assume I also assume that the North follows of
I also assume that the North follows of discrete distributed instead of causing
离散分布而不是导致分布器也只是获得此值，因为
discrete distributed instead of causing distributor also just get this value as
distributor also just get this value as this probability distribution value from
一些文献研究机构的这种概率分布值
this probability distribution value from some literature research government
some literature research government report or historical record just like
报告或历史记录就像是麦克风一样，所以选择了我在这里选择的
report or historical record just like it's a mic so chose I chose here however
it's a mic so chose I chose here however unfortunately those data I know it's
不幸的是，我知道这些数据非常重要，但是现在这些数据
unfortunately those data I know it's very important but this data is now
very important but this data is now we're not given in the paper that gave
这篇论文并没有给我们一个钦佩者竞争的机会，
we're not given in the paper that gave me an admirer to compete to do to
me an admirer to compete to do to continue so and forced us to do some
继续这样做，迫使我们做一些简化并做一些假设
continue so and forced us to do some simplification and do some assumptions
simplification and do some assumptions and try to take this hope
并尝试抱这个希望
在这里，让我们再次回到图形模型，现在我们必须
simplification and do some assumptions and try to take this hope
here here let's come back to the graphic model again and and now we have to
在这里，让我们再次回到图形模型，现在我们必须
model again and and now we have to everything ourselves first I want to do
首先要自己做所有事情，我想对此图形做一些简化
everything ourselves first I want to do some simplification for this graphical
some simplification for this graphical model if you example when you when you
如果您以身作则，当您看到决定的时候，我们将进行建模，我们将
model if you example when you when you see when you're deciding and we will
see when you're deciding and we will decide that is prefigured probability or
决定是预先确定的概率或建筑物损坏，您可以看到
decide that is prefigured probability or for the building damage you can see that
for the building damage you can see that it has swore parent 1 2 3 4 which I'm
它发誓父母1 2 3 4我是每个父母都有不同的状态
it has swore parent 1 2 3 4 which I'm the each parent has different state
the each parent has different state which means that that if you want to
这意味着，如果您要创建一个表，
which means that that if you want to create a table that will be a really
create a table that will be a really huge large table you have to input a lot
巨大的大表，您必须输入大量数据，而您处于高位
huge large table you have to input a lot of data and you are you are under high
of data and you are you are under high risk to make mistake and actually I made
冒犯错误的风险，实际上我犯了这个错误，但有趣的是，您去找他
risk to make mistake and actually I made that and but interesting you go to his
that and but interesting you go to his paper and check that the beauty talk and
纸并检查美容谈话和收缩是否几乎相似
paper and check that the beauty talk and the contraction has almost similar
the contraction has almost similar similar meanings so for simple to
具有相似的含义，因此为了简化此模型，我将其合并
similar meanings so for simple to simplify this this model I just combine
simplify this this model I just combine them together combined together and then
他们一起结合在一起，然后假设火智者知道我会
them together combined together and then assume that the the Firewise know I'll
assume that the the Firewise know I'll have three states inside and the yellow
里面有三个状态，黄色节点里面有牙膏，所以
have three states inside and the yellow node has toothpaste inside so that's
node has toothpaste inside so that's fair enough but and not gave me a
足够公平，但并没有给我一个噩梦，以违抗cpt以及
fair enough but and not gave me a nightmare to defy the cpt and also the
nightmare to defy the cpt and also the earth and independence assumption to
地球和独立性假设，以简化或主持这样的事
earth and independence assumption to simplify or chair or so okay like that
simplify or chair or so okay like that KB here's a very example is a very
KB这是一个非常示例，它是CPT的一个非常简单的示例，
KB here's a very example is a very simple example for one for CPT for the
simple example for one for CPT for the positional
位置这是灭火，它具有
positional this is a fire suppression and it has
this is a fire suppression and it has three parents and fire intensity this by
三个父母，火强度，根据实际健康状况，我将其定义为三个状态
three parents and fire intensity this by real health I define it as three states
real health I define it as three states and this too has has to stay inside so
这也必须留在里面，所以你
and this too has has to stay inside so you
buuuut this table you can sleep on the consider different states of different
buuuut这张桌子上可以睡，考虑不同状态的不同
consider different states of different parents and each island each elements in
父母和每个岛上表中的每个元素我都给了我们合理的
parents and each island each elements in the table I just gave our reasonable
the table I just gave our reasonable reasonable cats for the probability the
合理的猫对于概率，合理的含义是
reasonable cats for the probability the the meaning of reasonable is that for
the meaning of reasonable is that for example if you have a really low fire
例如，如果您的火势非常低并且建筑物正在磨损
example if you have a really low fire intensity and your building is wearing
intensity and your building is wearing the buildings very close to the fire
距离消防局非常近的建筑物，您被真正的包围
the buildings very close to the fire station and you are surrounded by really
station and you are surrounded by really at once the vault system which means to
马上，对于角色密度来说，金库系统非常高，您将
at once the vault system which means to the role density is very high you will
the role density is very high you will fight you will get better care better
战斗，消防部门会为您提供更好的护理和更好的健康
fight you will get better care better health from the fire department which
health from the fire department which means that the fire control could be
意味着火力控制可以是成功的，也可以是中等的，而不是差的
means that the fire control could be successful or medium instead of poor so
successful or medium instead of poor so for example this case I just gave the
例如，在这种情况下，我只是给穷人穷人，四个州可以
for example this case I just gave the poor poor can the four states has a
poor poor can the four states has a really low I give him a really low
非常低，我给他的概率非常低，并且控制了中位数
really low I give him a really low probability and gave the medians control
probability and gave the medians control and successful control a really high
成功控制的可能性非常高，所以现在我们建立或
and successful control a really high probability so now we built our or
probability so now we built our or graphic model and also also have our
图形模型，并且每个模型都有我们的概率分布表
graphic model and also also have our probability distribution table for each
probability distribution table for each note the next stop Ahmet life is to make
请注意，Ahmet生活的下一站是在这里制造所有推理引擎。
note the next stop Ahmet life is to make all the inference engine here in this
all the inference engine here in this problem which 408 y31 see the first line
408 y31看到的第一行是连接树和推理引擎的问题
problem which 408 y31 see the first line is the junction tree an inference engine
is the junction tree an inference engine and neither one has to be belief
而且没有人必须是信仰传播引擎，我们已经谈论了很多
and neither one has to be belief propagation engine we have talked a lot
propagation engine we have talked a lot in the class and the tribe test allows
在课堂上，部落测试允许家庭作业，所以我不会讨论这个
in the class and the tribe test allows in the homework so I won't discuss this
in the homework so I won't discuss this too much there and there is another
那里太多了，还有一点滞留可以使用
too much there and there is another little bit detention to use to use
little bit detention to use to use sampling engine called likelihood
采样引擎称为似然等待立点铰接
sampling engine called likelihood waiting standpoint hinging
waiting standpoint hinging so it's a kind of temporal inking the
所以这是一种暂时的墨水，样本引擎的基本思想是
so it's a kind of temporal inking the basic idea of sample engines are you
basic idea of sample engines are you just the cheapest and whole handle turns
只是最便宜和完整的转弯，它们来自您的贝叶斯
just the cheapest and whole handle turns they're from your from your Bayesian
they're from your from your Bayesian network and to compute the probability
网络并计算此庙宇计算机古庙宇的概率
network and to compute the probability of this temple computer ancient temple
of this temple computer ancient temple Allah keeps temple in now if you get
如果您获得足够的样本，安拉将使神殿现在处于最终状态
Allah keeps temple in now if you get enough sample the final distribution of
enough sample the final distribution of your sampling would be close to the true
您的抽样将接近基本分布的真实分布
your sampling would be close to the true distribution that's a basic idea of
distribution that's a basic idea of sampling and likelihood likelihood
采样和似然似然等待采样完成
sampling and likelihood likelihood waiting sampling is done it will be
waiting sampling is done it will be updated sampling work it's just we have
更新的采样工作只是我们有证据，因此需要
updated sampling work it's just we have the evidence and it takes to have this
the evidence and it takes to have this variable and only sample the one above
变量，仅是上面的一个是可穿戴变量，与
variable and only sample the one above is a wearable variables not related to
is a wearable variables not related to the average not only samples and man
平均不仅是样本和人为证据变量，而且每个样本
the average not only samples and man evidence variables and for each sample
evidence variables and for each sample we just multiply it by the weight which
我们将其乘以权重就可以了，我已经使用了很多文献资料
we just multiply it by the weight which is fine I've used a lot of literature's
is fine I've used a lot of literature's talk about the likelihood waiting
谈论可能性等待等待等待等待推论和
talk about the likelihood waiting waiting waiting waiting inference and
waiting waiting waiting inference and the sums up term are very complicated
总结期非常复杂，这里包含很多信息
the sums up term are very complicated and contain a lot of information here I
and contain a lot of information here I adjust the last day introduced by using
通过使用一个简单的示例来调整最后一天的介绍，让我们回来
adjust the last day introduced by using a simple simple example let's come back
a simple simple example let's come back our cream-coloured sprinkler model we
我们的奶油色洒水模型，我们担心熟悉的垃圾
our cream-coloured sprinkler model we are which we are worried familiar waste
are which we are worried familiar waste so and assume that we are required to
因此，假设我们需要计算R的R的概率，其中
so and assume that we are required to compute the probability of R of R which
compute the probability of R of R which is ring given as is true that cream
给出的戒指是正确的，奶油色是2，白色的草是真的
is ring given as is true that cream color is 2 and the white grass is true
color is 2 and the white grass is true and let's start or simply first wish you
让我们开始或只是简单地希望您简单地看到质量就没有了
and let's start or simply first wish you the simple see the quality there is no
the simple see the quality there is no country and say we just assume that we
国家，并说我们只是假设我们可以称其为真，请
country and say we just assume that we can call it as true which please
can call it as true which please what which is plastic
什么是可塑的，以及妻子在我们决定时的感觉
what which is plastic and the sense this wife's decide when we
and the sense this wife's decide when we will next with simple the simple sighs
接下来，我们将以简单的简单叹息来介绍，既然有了威士忌风格，我们就可以
will next with simple the simple sighs so since whiskey style we have we can
so since whiskey style we have we can only offer to like our eyes from this
只提供从右后方喜欢我们的眼睛的感觉，但是冰厚了
only offer to like our eyes from this right back however the ice is thick by
right back however the ice is thick by the evidence which is true so we can
证据是真实的，所以我们只能在第一点上取得更大的成功
the evidence which is true so we can only strike the wider of point one then
only strike the wider of point one then because our first weight of point one
因为我们的第一个点的权重然后到达我们的实例的味道
because our first weight of point one and then come to our instance tastes
and then come to our instance tastes simple which is part so we can only like
很简单，这是一部分，因此我们只能喜欢此栏右框中的值，
simple which is part so we can only like our values from this bar right box and
our values from this bar right box and and there is no constraint on heart
对心脏没有任何约束，这意味着我们可以发送
and there is no constraint on heart which means that we can send off
which means that we can send off whatever we want
我们想要的就是让我们假设简单的艺术是
whatever we want let's assume that with simple art is
let's assume that with simple art is true are true and then we move to
true是true，然后我们以表格为例，说我们的眼睛
true are true and then we move to example the table and says the our eyes
example the table and says the our eyes way is for that to be true
方式是使我们真实，我们的样本是真实的，然后回来
way is for that to be true our is sample to be true and come back
our is sample to be true and come back to the evidence we record W to be true
证明我们将W记录为真，因此表只能是W
to the evidence we record W to be true so because the table can be only only it
so because the table can be only only it can be only in 9.99
只能在9.99，而我们最终发现了另一种方式
can be only in 9.99 and we caught another way finally our
and we caught another way finally our total weight is 0.1 multiplied 199 which
总重量是0.1乘以199，即今晚的0.09，我们只是
total weight is 0.1 multiplied 199 which is 0.09 tonight and we just just
is 0.09 tonight and we just just multiplied and just multiply our sample
乘以我们的样本，然后乘以这就是我们的样本乘以该权重
multiplied and just multiply our sample with this is our sample by this weight
with this is our sample by this weight and then to a lot of iterations to trim
然后经过很多次迭代来精简您的工作，最后猫得到了结果
and then to a lot of iterations to trim your job and finally the cat's a result
your job and finally the cat's a result of the final of probability and catch
最后的概率并抓住这一点，存在一些问题
of the final of probability and catch this one there is some problem of
this one there is some problem of likelihood waiting for example if you
似然等待，例如，如果您需要计算T的概率
likelihood waiting for example if you are required to compute probability of T
are required to compute probability of T given I signed the are you are what
鉴于我签署的是你是你担心的东西，也许有时候
given I signed the are you are what you're worried you can maybe sometimes
you're worried you can maybe sometimes thousands thousands go well with
成千上万的证据
thousands thousands go well with evidence
evidence sans use the the U star U star sample
不使用U形星，U形星的样本，在这里您无需查看
sans use the the U star U star sample its sample to see here you don't need to
its sample to see here you don't need to think about the as your evidence which
考虑一下，作为您的证据，这是非常沉默的哦，是的，有一些
think about the as your evidence which is a silent awfully oh yeah there's some
is a silent awfully oh yeah there's some opted for the sampling for under some
选择了一些其他采样更改下的采样来修复它
opted for the sampling for under some some other sampling changings to fix it
some other sampling changings to fix it problem which I won't talk here here's
这是我一生中得到的结果，我在这里不谈
problem which I won't talk here here's the result I got from the my life and
the result I got from the my life and this this part on the left-hand side I
这部分在左侧，我只是图片烧伤，我很少为零
this this part on the left-hand side I just the picture burn I rare to be zero
just the picture burn I rare to be zero point zero two zero point zero one
点零二零点零一公里平方
point zero two zero point zero one kilometer square and the changing the
kilometer square and the changing the fire intensity the actual painting
火灾强度实际涂装成本的变化或
fire intensity the actual painting change for the cost or the cost that's
change for the cost or the cost that's because I assume last things as a higher
因为我认为最后一件事是因为火势较高
because I assume last things as a higher in fire intensity has a really really
in fire intensity has a really really low very low probabilities and this part
低非常低的概率，这部分在右侧，我只是修复了
low very low probabilities and this part on the right hand side I just fix the
on the right hand side I just fix the fire intensity to be this one and the
火灾强度是这一和不断变化的高层美术师表现出的
fire intensity to be this one and the changing the upper area artist showed
changing the upper area artist showed generally those increasing trend as a
通常，随着燃烧面积的增加，这些增加的趋势使得
generally those increasing trend as a function of burn area that makes the
function of burn area that makes the instance if you have a fire intensity
例如，如果您有火势并且燃烧面积较大，那么您的结果
instance if you have a fire intensity and have a larger burn area your result
and have a larger burn area your result would be a little your cost will be a
会有点你的成本会有点大，这次民意调查也
would be a little your cost will be a little bit large and this poll also
little bit large and this poll also showed the photos do something for
展示了照片为我们所知道的不同推理引擎做了些什么
showed the photos do something for different inference engines that we know
different inference engines that we know the junction Creek and of accurate
交界处的小河和精确的变化以及PD的发布和
the junction Creek and of accurate changing and the PD publication and
changing and the PD publication and likely who waiting proximate engines you
可能是谁在等待附近的引擎，您可以看到这种情况下
likely who waiting proximate engines you can see that for this case the chance to
can see that for this case the chance to be worthwhile where we always compared
值得在我们总是将其与您知道信念的交界处进行比较的地方
be worthwhile where we always compared to the junction you know the belief
to the junction you know the belief complication works very well and there's
并发症非常有效，有一些
complication works very well and there's some
some different but between the likely who to
有所不同，但可能在结点树的谁和这一信念之间
different but between the likely who to the junction tree and this one belief
the junction tree and this one belief propagation works also worried well but
传播工作也很担心，但除了这里还可以
propagation works also worried well but except here okay
except here okay the beautiful tools to the similar work
普拉达（Prada）类似作品的漂亮工具，但其中有成千上万个细胞
the beautiful tools to the similar work Prada but all the thousands of cells in
Prada but all the thousands of cells in on the island you can end up with this
在岛上，您甚至有可能在这种习俗中最终会遭受这种破坏的习俗
on the island you can end up with this damaged custom at might even to learn in
damaged custom at might even to learn in the project they also just separates
他们也只是将这个岛分割成9000个小岛的项目
the project they also just separates this island to nine thousand little
this island to nine thousand little cells though I don't have enough time to
牢房，尽管我没有足够的时间去做爱尔兰菜
cells though I don't have enough time to do Irish to do Irish a for the whole
do Irish to do Irish a for the whole island so this one just give you our
岛，所以这只是给您关于最终结果的提示，并且
island so this one just give you our hints about the final result which and
hints about the final result which and there are some other thing we can talk
还有其他一些我们可以谈及的东西，以及颤抖的质量
there are some other thing we can talk and the quality of trembling as a
and the quality of trembling as a function of number of your sample so you
样本数的函数，以便您可以幸运地看到
function of number of your sample so you can see that the likelihood luckily
can see that the likelihood luckily who's awaiting awaiting inference
谁在等待推理引擎的结果接近
who's awaiting awaiting inference engines results come close to the
engines results come close to the junction sweet results the difference
结甜效果差请娇小适当
junction sweet results the difference please the petite the appropriate a
please the petite the appropriate a difference that means the difference
差异意味着连接树和可能性之间的差异
difference that means the difference between junction tree and likelihood
between junction tree and likelihood reading so if you increase your number
阅读，因此，如果您增加采样数量，则会减少
reading so if you increase your number of sampling you will reduce the
of sampling you will reduce the difference which means the likelihood
差异，这意味着接近结点树的可能性
difference which means the likelihood close to the close to the junction tree
close to the close to the junction tree however there is no freelance and if you
但是没有自由职业者，如果您增加数量，则增加您的
however there is no freelance and if you increase your number of increase your
increase your number of increase your time okay okay
时间好吧好吧未来世界肯定有一些未来的工作
time okay okay future world some future work definitely
future world some future work definitely for the work of this welfare study you
对于这项福利研究的工作，您肯定可以添加更多信息
for the work of this welfare study you can definitely add more information more
can definitely add more information more cost more nodes and each note you can
花费更多的节点，您可以将每个音符分隔成更多的空间，
cost more nodes and each note you can separate into more space that will
separate into more space that will definitely increase your accuracy of
肯定会提高近似的准确性，我也认为
definitely increase your accuracy of your approximation and I also think
your approximation and I also think about think about the for my own
考虑为自己的研究也考虑我可以的一种方法
about think about the for my own research also think about one way I can
research also think about one way I can maybe who I can I can apply what I've
也许我可以将我从这笔费用中学到的知识运用到我的研究中
maybe who I can I can apply what I've learned in this cost in my research
learned in this cost in my research to do some more uncertainty vacation for
为我的实验做更多不确定的假期，这会很有趣
to do some more uncertainty vacation for my experiments that would be interesting
my experiments that would be interesting to conclude today's presentation first
结束今天的演示文稿的第一个查询简单项目是一个主题
to conclude today's presentation first inquiry simple project is a single topic
inquiry simple project is a single topic compared to you guys may be busy Network
与你们相比可能很忙网络在其中确实很强大
compared to you guys may be busy Network definitely really strong for in which
definitely really strong for in which you can use to you to evaluate the fire
您可以使用它来评估火井火灾后果，我也认为
you can use to you to evaluate the fire well fire consequence and I'm also think
well fire consequence and I'm also think about one way to apply it to my own
一种将其应用于我自己的研究以及忙碌和忙碌的优势的方法
about one way to apply it to my own research and the advantage of busy and
research and the advantage of busy and network is is ability to power
网络是增强来自不同区域各方的信息的能力
network is is ability to power information from different area parties
information from different area parties to worry computational expense if you
如果您构建一个很大的网络，就不必担心计算成本
to worry computational expense if you build a really large piece their network
build a really large piece their network and create you have also you need to do
并创建您自己，您还需要做很多工作才能找到合适的
and create you have also you need to do a lot of work to find the apt and since
a lot of work to find the apt and since the separatists are known for this for
分离主义者之所以闻名，是因为对方没有在我们的论文中给我
the separatists are known for this for the other didn't give me in the paper we
the other didn't give me in the paper we can now compute our result with the with
现在可以使用，而没有和的作者洞穴计算我们的结果。
can now compute our result with the with the authors cave without and and another
the authors cave without and and another two chances I act exact approximation
我有两次机会完全按照这种精确方法行事，另一种是
two chances I act exact approximation this exact approach and another to
this exact approach and another to proximate approaches and
最近的方法和
[掌声]
this exact approach and another to proximate approaches and
[Applause]
是啊是啊
yeah yeah
[音乐]
[Music]
哦
Oh
所以他问我，解释该部分的计算量最大的是哪里
so he asked me where's the most the computation who explains the part for
computation who explains the part for the junction tree to compute I think
要计算的结点树，我认为我不知道没有分数
the junction tree to compute I think that the I don't know no score exactly I
that the I don't know no score exactly I think if my answer is salad maybe in the
想想如果我的答案是沙拉，也许在路口树中，您必须运行
think if my answer is salad maybe in the junction tree you have to we run the
junction tree you have to we run the code you have to find the optimize the
您必须找到用于优化生日的有偏交界树的代码
code you have to find the optimize the biased junction tree for the birthday
biased junction tree for the birthday for your model so maybe that will be
为您的模型，所以也许会在某个时候调用它，或者在计算上
for your model so maybe that will be called sometime or it is computationally
called sometime or it is computationally expensive
昂贵的
我不是我没有在这里做得那么深
called sometime or it is computationally expensive
I didn't I didn't do that deeply here
我是银河系便利课程的二年级学生，现在拥有
I'm a second year student in galactic convenience I'm in possession and today
convenience I'm in possession and today my turn project linear time algorithm in
基于高斯的贝叶斯电子邮件引擎中的我的转项目线性时间算法
my turn project linear time algorithm in Bayesian email engine based on Gaussian
Deltora设置了动画噪点，我确实有两个步骤，首先是料斗参数
Deltora is animating noisy I really have two steps first is the hopper parameter
two steps first is the hopper parameter estimation by yeah matters
是的估计很重要
期望最大化，第二个将是AP的图像恢复
two steps first is the hopper parameter estimation by yeah matters
expectation maximization and second that will be the image restoration by an AP
期望最大化，第二个将是AP的图像恢复
will be the image restoration by an AP maximize a posterior metric and in this
最大化后验度量，在此
那些需要环境方差矩阵逆的事物发生变化
will be the image restoration by an AP maximize a posterior metric and in this
those things change that requires inverse of environment variance matrix
那些需要环境方差矩阵逆的事物发生变化
inverse of environment variance matrix the computation under order of natives
根据厄尼博客的本地人顺序的计算我需要这个
the computation under order of natives order of Ernie blogging I need this
order of Ernie blogging I need this people achieve
人们实现
之所以这样，是因为实际上与我们能学到的东西有关
order of Ernie blogging I need this people achieve
the reason why is because virtually having related to what we can learn
之所以这样，是因为实际上与我们能学到的东西有关
having related to what we can learn about the past like GM adoption my
关于过去，例如通用汽车的领养，我的父亲和恐吓的笑声，以及
about the past like GM adoption my father and intimidation laughter and
father and intimidation laughter and second reason is that it's highly
第二个原因是，这与我在这里做的事情高度相关
second reason is that it's highly related to what i'm doing here i'm doing
related to what i'm doing here i'm doing the noted image alignment and the melty
着名的图像对齐方式和融化的图像显影是最好的方法
the noted image alignment and the melty image development it is the best way to
image development it is the best way to show my my algorithm itself so I'm
显示我自己的算法本身，所以我非常有兴趣选择出色的算法
show my my algorithm itself so I'm really interested to choose excellent
really interested to choose excellent clarity in both insurance caps and the
保险限额和参数设置都非常清楚
clarity in both insurance caps and the parameter settings it's very clear for
parameter settings it's very clear for me to follow each step so I will not go
我按照每个步骤进行操作，这样我就不会陷入循环或者不知道发生了什么
me to follow each step so I will not go into a loop or I don't know what's going
into a loop or I don't know what's going on
上
本报告我们仅介绍了成帧器在18年内接待了他们，第二次
into a loop or I don't know what's going on
this report our first introduced the framers hoste them in 18 only and second
本报告我们仅介绍了成帧器在18年内接待了他们，第二次
framers hoste them in 18 only and second how are you to introduce you their
您如何向您介绍他们的线性时间算法？
how are you to introduce you their linear time algorithm second I add a
linear time algorithm second I add a comparison other rhythm to do this paper
比较其他节奏做这篇论文增加以前的论文唯一
comparison other rhythm to do this paper increase in previous paper the only
increase in previous paper the only averaging everything else which is just
将其他所有内容平均化，以单位为单位，然后除以
averaging everything else which is just as units together and divide to the
as units together and divide to the remember a free print so I think too
记得有免费印刷品，所以我认为太简单了，以至于无法显示更多功能
remember a free print so I think too simple I thought to show more features
simple I thought to show more features of this outer limits them so I added the
这个外部限制了他们，所以我添加了一个名为利比亚3d的问题，原始的是
of this outer limits them so I added the matter called Libyan 3d the original is
matter called Libyan 3d the original is very long it's a video Facebook noising
很长一段时间，这是一段视频，Facebook告别了再见的传承历史，是真实的
very long it's a video Facebook noising bye-bye passage history being truthful
bye-bye passage history being truthful it's very longer recorded vivianne 3d
它记录的维维安3d时间更长，应该有这种方法
it's very longer recorded vivianne 3d and this method should there be result
and this method should there be result in any papers so I want to show the
在任何论文中，我想展示其他人之间的比较
in any papers so I want to show the comparison between the people other
comparison between the people other algorithm in this paper and Libyan 3d
本文的算法和利比亚3D最后，我将向您展示按摩，而我们
algorithm in this paper and Libyan 3d last I will show you the massage and we
last I will show you the massage and we can discuss the results
可以讨论给出给定原始图像的结果
can discuss the results given given an original image composed
given given an original image composed of we buy the kid for a depleted image
我们为孩子购买的是与原始图片大小相同的已耗尽图片，
of we buy the kid for a depleted image of the same size of the original one is
of the same size of the original one is generated by adding additive white
通过将原始高斯白噪声awgn加到原始噪声中而产生
generated by adding additive white Gaussian noise awgn to the original one
Gaussian noise awgn to the original one suppose we independently of team K
假设我们独立于K队而降低了形象，并且他大于一个
suppose we independently of team K degrade image and he is bigger than one
degrade image and he is bigger than one we denoted the original image by the
我们用水标记了原始图像，因此实际上是在想像您
we denoted the original image by the water so it is actually imagined you
water so it is actually imagined you just vectorized into a vector to
只是向量化为一个向量以简化计算，它具有n
just vectorized into a vector to simplify the computation and it has n
simplify the computation and it has n pick stars
摘星星[音乐]
pick stars [Music]
[Music] skin roll a burrito you know to the case
皮肤卷一个卷饼，你知道到案件由rector降低图像的情况下，我会
skin roll a burrito you know to the case degraded image by the rector next I will
degraded image by the rector next I will introduce the definition of prior
介绍方形网格图v5的先验分布的定义
introduce the definition of prior distribution for v5 a square grid graph
distribution for v5 a square grid graph TV in the refuge's of arrivals you know
在庇护所中的电视，您知道在以斯拉半岛，E是边缘地带，因此
TV in the refuge's of arrivals you know it in Ezra and E is the edge so the
it in Ezra and E is the edge so the prior distribution is defined as
先验分布定义为
在7月2日，以
it in Ezra and E is the edge so the prior distribution is defined as
on July 2 the broth it's represented by the movement of
在7月2日，以
it's represented by the movement of energy functions
能量函数
我发誓
it's represented by the movement of energy functions
as I as I swear
参数团队Yaya和alpha是我们要采取的行动
the parameter team Yaya and alpha is the we want to act
we want to act the contract is
合同是
这是因为很好，这是人们尝试解决问题的方法，
we want to act the contract is
this is because well it was people try the matter and the waves and complete
这是因为很好，这是人们尝试解决问题的方法，
the matter and the waves and complete routine to the inverse of this
这种甲壳动物的反例，自然而然的成功
routine to the inverse of this crustacean a success in doing by natural
crustacean a success in doing by natural decomposition
分解
在Moodle办公室的模型中
crustacean a success in doing by natural decomposition
in the model of the Moodle office
awgn现在我们准备找到后验分布
the awgn now we are ready to find the posterior distribution
和
and
我们可以做的
we can do
女士职位，这意味着lambda的利润率
ladies position that means the profit margin lambda
因为我们已经有了我们以前的发行版，
since we're already having our prior distribution and
通过EMS搜索薰衣草
the lavenders by EMS search
太平洋将在那里发挥作用，我们发现与Maxine的联系
Pacific that will be there to function we find a connection with to Maxine
we find a connection with to Maxine is illustrate the use of all production
是说明所有生产后验分布的用法，我们加入了
is illustrate the use of all production posterior distribution are we join the
posterior distribution are we join the group
组以及我们定义为哪些特殊能力
group and what special abilities we define as
and what special abilities we define as the production
生产
我们将为每个需要计算的协方差的反函数进行计算
and what special abilities we define as the production
we will compute for each requires the inverse of the covariance magic makes
我们将为每个需要计算的协方差的反函数进行计算
inverse of the covariance magic makes the computation time is thank you
计算时间是谢谢
用于图像恢复
inverse of the covariance magic makes the computation time is thank you
for the image restoration
时间到了，谢谢
time is and thank you
非常喜欢它们导致场景的抗扰度近似验证
really like the immunity approximation validation they lead to a scene
我们实际要做的是
what do we actually do is
萨维克式的牧场主与老与老的突变时间一
Saavik type of ranchers and old and the old on the mutation time a
对我来说，整个算法需要做的是部分算法
what to me the whole algorithm what we need to do is the partial
what we need to do is the partial derivatives in another energy the energy
衍生出另一种能量，火的能量
derivatives in another energy the energy of the fire
至于胜利能量的传单
as for the Flyers for the triumph energy
没有Allison Stockport这个装置，但我是Alice
no Allison Stockport this device but I is Alice
我们知道它的引力可以写成
we know the gravity it can be written as
类似地
similarly the for the area
绝对决定矩阵的行列式
for the determinants of decision matrix absolutely
真的是导数
really the derivative
其实非常嘿，请收敛13
actually very hey it converged please like them 13
hey it converged please like them 13 iterations and the here
迭代，这里我将首先向您保证它是补丁
iterations and the here I will first assure you it's the patch
I will first assure you it's the patch faced the baby and three
面对婴儿和三个
但总的来说，
I will first assure you it's the patch faced the baby and three
but in total we have up to
女士们生活在其中，我们保留作为王子的说唱歌手之一
ladies to live in that we keep the one of the decree the Prince as the rapper
在第一部分中只是所有项目的平均值
in the first part is just for the average of all the projects
average of all the projects and the second part is actually is to
第二部分实际上是衰减位置的频率
and the second part is actually is to attenuate the frequency for positions
attenuate the frequency for positions that do not match the record and it is
与记录不匹配的是
辛西娅常数这个修正常数实际上是迟钝的
attenuate the frequency for positions that do not match the record and it is
Cynthia is constant this fix the constant actually is
辛西娅常数这个修正常数实际上是迟钝的
constant actually is where is the noise variance would
在素材功能中，噪声方差会在哪里激活？
where is the noise variance would activate in the footage function we
activate in the footage function we believe is the difference between the
相信是说唱歌手的触动之间的区别
believe is the difference between the touch of the rapper's
这是您制作的渐变噪声数为3的结果，
and here is the result for the number of the gradient noise you make is 3 and the
the gradient noise you make is 3 and the include noise variance is their tape
包含噪声方差是他们的磁带图像大小是2到5 6 x 2 pi
include noise variance is their tape image size is 2 to 5 6 by 2 pi
我以此来显示他们的结果，他要求我今晚讲种族，并要求有
I show their results by it he asked I speak tonight racial and asked to have
I speak tonight racial and asked to have dr. Shri Mataji
博士什里·马塔吉（Shri Mataji）
因为我是ger队的饲养者，所以助推器花了很多时间，所以如果你还记得的话
I speak tonight racial and asked to have dr. Shri Mataji
the Boosters ts the time as I am the feeder of the Badgers so if you remember
因为我是ger队的饲养者，所以助推器花了很多时间，所以如果你还记得的话
feeder of the Badgers so if you remember the largely work to the wrong tree
对错误树的大部分工作
[音乐]
feeder of the Badgers so if you remember the largely work to the wrong tree
[Music]
是较大图像尺寸的结果5到5哦
is the result for bigger image size Oh 5 to 5
让我向您展示更大的形象
let me show you the even bigger image
是的
yes
由医生摆动两次
swing by the doctor twice
还要考虑一下我刚才在英国队长的讲话。
also consider the English team leader I I just popped the remark from the
I just popped the remark from the teenage member from zero enough
少年成员从零开始
否则
I just popped the remark from the teenage member from zero enough
the otherwise
我们之间的所有三场比赛
all our three matches between that
that forever after leaving my village
永远离开我的村庄永远
forever after leaving my village immediately
immediately fifty
五十
愚弄线性记录中的两点
immediately fifty
fool on the linear record out of two points
愚弄线性记录中的两点
points these more amazing wonders
这些更奇妙的奇观，是的，它们彼此非常接近
these more amazing wonders yeah they are very close to each other
根据管理局的赔偿金可能会过期
according to Authority benamber may be expiated
expiated I also tie the image type the previous
我也将上个月的图片类型扎起来，比如说要买五五次
I also tie the image type the previous month like five five runs to buy I
month like five five runs to buy I wanted things they happen maybe the
想要发生的事情，也许是正确的生活，愿景实际上是好的
wanted things they happen maybe the right life the vision actually is good
right life the vision actually is good in the bean bag is not inclusive that
豆袋中的价格和机会不包含在内，因此
in the bean bag is not inclusive that price and opportunity so it's
price and opportunity so it's preventively welcome
预防性地欢迎
这个线性时间也不能最成功地解析出精美的图像，
price and opportunity so it's preventively welcome
this linear time neither can you resolve a nice image most successfully than
这个线性时间也不能最成功地解析出精美的图像，
a nice image most successfully than aberration answered all the time in all
在所有情况下，像差总是回答鞭打者对小物体的尝试。
aberration answered all the time in all cases for lasher's tries on the small
cases for lasher's tries on the small amount of teammates read the amps medium
队友阅读安培中号3d是小电池嫩线性
amount of teammates read the amps medium 3d is the little battery tender linear
3d is the little battery tender linear time but for the larger amount of image
时间，但对于大量图像，线性问题意义深远
time but for the larger amount of image linear matters profound
也许猫头鹰早于硒雅典，而不是让人惊叹的国家
maybe the owl earlier the selenium Athens rather than amazing of countries
Athens rather than amazing of countries in my legs
在我的腿上
所以你的姿势就是为什么分钟数会引起注意
Athens rather than amazing of countries in my legs
so your posture is why the number of minutes notice
让我们玩方程式二
let's play of equation two
如果您有分配，甚至还有期权和大类人猿
if you have a distribution or even for the options and the big hominoid
the options and the big hominoid be affected by the tsunami the marries
受到海啸的影响，喧闹的噪音不会令西格玛广场感到高兴
be affected by the tsunami the marries of noise won't be pleased Sigma square
of noise won't be pleased Sigma square well if you crease the into Sigma square
好吧，如果您将其折成Sigma正方形，那么您就在其中，所以您越多
well if you crease the into Sigma square a you're in it so the more the more you
a you're in it so the more the more you makes you get Latino is very you have so
让您变得拉丁裔非常拥有，所以他们想添加一些东西
makes you get Latino is very you have so is something like they'd like to add
is something like they'd like to add them together and the the the noise
他们在一起和噪声方差
them together and the the the noise variance
你是说一个饼干吗
would you mean a cookie
如果这是932 NASA在所有问题上的区别，
if it's difference between the 932 NASA wonder for all of the matter the
wonder for all of the matter the computation time will increase
计算时间将增加原住民单位的数量
computation time will increase the number of units for the aboriginal
the number of units for the aboriginal it's very small always lifestyle website
这个很小的网站始终都是生活时尚网站，因为您没有那样做，
it's very small always lifestyle website because you didn't do that keep
because you didn't do that keep syntactic it has to actually add them
语法上必须将它们实际加在一起，但另一方面
syntactic it has to actually add them together but for the other matter it
together but for the other matter it really depends depends on the speech of
真的取决于物质的表达
really depends depends on the speech of matter
我找到它了
I find it
图片成员越多，他们的主人的计算时间就比我们少
with more image members the living their master has less computation time than we
master has less computation time than we do you have
你有没有
哦，大家好，我的名字叫露西（Lucy），就像我来自航空航天业一样，
master has less computation time than we do you have
oh hello everyone my name is Lucy same way I'm from the aerospace and
哦，大家好，我的名字叫露西（Lucy），就像我来自航空航天业一样，
way I'm from the aerospace and mechanical engineering taking this
机械工程学这门课虽然有点冷但是很棒
mechanical engineering taking this course it's kind of cold but a great
course it's kind of cold but a great challenge for me and it's my pleasure to
挑战对我来说，我很乐意做有关交付的演讲
challenge for me and it's my pleasure to do my presentation about delivering
do my presentation about delivering using the things I learned in the car I
使用我在车上学到的东西，我这样做是因为它非常有趣
using the things I learned in the car I do this because of its very interesting
do this because of its very interesting project on the website so when we
网站上的项目，因此当我们认为应该花力气时，我们可以找到一个
project on the website so when we thought should be laboring we can find a
thought should be laboring we can find a lot of examples we can the most famous
我们可以举很多例子，最有名的女人是加州理工学院1:01的标签
lot of examples we can the most famous woman is a Caltech 1:01 the labels
woman is a Caltech 1:01 the labels airplanes or other object tools in our
我们日常生活中的飞机或其他物体工具，例如椅子或桌子或
airplanes or other object tools in our daily lives like a chair or table or
daily lives like a chair or table or whatever you can say of recently there's
不管你怎么说，最近还有另一种爱的形象，他们将它们标记为
whatever you can say of recently there's another image love love they label these
another image love love they label these birds and they can characterize about
鸟类，它们可以描述其中的任何一个，这也是为什么
birds and they can characterize about either and this is also the reason why
either and this is also the reason why we do this labeling before because if
我们之前做过这个标签，因为如果您想知道这是什么，您首先
we do this labeling before because if you want to know what this is you first
you want to know what this is you first have to label yet you have a big picture
必须贴上标签，但您有一幅大图，然后我们必须说出对象在哪里
have to label yet you have a big picture then we have to say where is the object
then we have to say where is the object this is a primary step
这是我们在可以渲染的Google上进行搜索时的第一步
this is a primary step when we search on Google who can render
when we search on Google who can render some papers they talk about this project
他们谈论这个项目的一些论文请真正的产品，这是一个
some papers they talk about this project please kind of true product it is a
please kind of true product it is a customer Redmond field and we have great
客户雷蒙德（Redmond）领域，我们有很好的观察和关于
customer Redmond field and we have great observations and the hidden value about
observations and the hidden value about the hand observe reservations image and
手观察保留图像和流行的方法是迭代的
the hand observe reservations image and popular methods are iterative
popular methods are iterative conditional mode this Laster we have a
有条件的模式这Laster我们会在您执行此操作时进行人为操作
conditional mode this Laster we have a homework in human to when you do this
homework in human to when you do this this is the beginning of this project
这是这个项目的开始，然后根据这些，我们可以做
this is the beginning of this project then based on these at the end we can do
then based on these at the end we can do a graphic art and god Carter actually it
一个图形艺术和卡特神，实际上它不仅可以应用在这个想法上，
a graphic art and god Carter actually it can be applied not only on this idea we
can be applied not only on this idea we can also applied on Vicki and thousand
也可以应用于维琪和一千种方法，因为增长的趋势
can also applied on Vicki and thousand methods because the growth current
methods because the growth current basically it can kill a lot of cool
基本上，它可以杀死很多很酷的像素，不仅是一个像素，然后
basically it can kill a lot of cool pixels not only one pixels and then
pixels not only one pixels and then distill method I will talk about is the
我将讨论的提炼方法是他认为传播的循环
distill method I will talk about is the loop he believes to propagation
海报工作人员赶上了沉积金属的大师和一个高级大师
poster staffer to catch the master depositing metal and an advanced master
depositing metal and an advanced master that would be sequential train waited
这将是基于
that would be sequential train waited message conference which is based on
message conference which is based on Avicii and when I talk about this method
Avicii，当我谈论这种方法时，希望您能告诉我我错了
Avicii and when I talk about this method I hope you can tell me where I'm wrong
I hope you can tell me where I'm wrong because we can say this equation in our
因为我们可以说我们工作部分中的这个等式是总的
because we can say this equation in our work part is observed by the total
work part is observed by the total energy the Sun from the observation and
从观察到能量太阳和邻居最重要
energy the Sun from the observation and the neighbor neighbor the most important
the neighbor neighbor the most important part is
在此标签下，零件实际上既很重要
part is actually both important under this label
actually both important under this label will be actual consume the states naval
将是我们实际消耗的各州海军储备信息
will be actual consume the states naval reserve information we came out to
reserve information we came out to change because it is what would help and
变化，因为这将有所帮助，并且有人总结了这两个部分，
change because it is what would help and by some summarizes these two parts to
by some summarizes these two parts to have a total energy and whether accept
有总的精力，是否接受是否有吸引力
have a total energy and whether accept or not attractive is the picked
or not attractive is the picked alternative decided by the energy
由能量决定的替代方案，它是减少还是增加
alternative decided by the energy whether it's decrease or increase in the
whether it's decrease or increase in the Angela will have lowest damages when we
当我们转动所有像素时，安吉拉的伤害将最低，并且我们会做很多
Angela will have lowest damages when we turn all the pixels and we do a lot of
图像以及权重因素都来自青铜器的保存
images and also the weighting factors work from the preservation of bronze
work from the preservation of bronze neighbor we can till this part we
邻居，我们可以直到这部分我们增加或在图像的分割下
neighbor we can till this part we increase or under the division the image
increase or under the division the image will be different and then I will talk
会有所不同，然后我将谈谈双方的图形卡
will be different and then I will talk about the graph card both parties are
about the graph card both parties are for this part we tune with those colors
对于这一部分，我们用这些颜色进行调整，就像冷冻机一样，
for this part we tune with those colors it's like a freezer we cut through these
it's like a freezer we cut through these parts and was an account or not it's
零件，是否是一个帐户，如果Y，也用能量来描述
parts and was an account or not it's also described by the energy if Y
also described by the energy if Y invalid in brought carton 2000 army just
在带入的纸箱2000军中无效，只是重新计算能量，但是它将
invalid in brought carton 2000 army just calculate the energy again but it will
calculate the energy again but it will be more computational cost because the
由于邻居数量增加，计算成本更高
be more computational cost because the number of neighbors is enlarged the one
number of neighbors is enlarged the one I do this record and if I increase the
我做这个记录，如果我增加了说的大小，或者如果我想扔的话，则增加D
I do this record and if I increase the say the size or the D if I want to throw
say the size or the D if I want to throw up a lot of pixels and tram will be very
像素很多，电车对于一些复杂的设备可能不是很好
up a lot of pixels and tram will be very maybe not very good for some complicated
maybe not very good for some complicated applications but it's very effective
应用程序，但非常有效
在我的书房里，我并不惊讶不向聚会广播这是
maybe not very good for some complicated applications but it's very effective
in my study I didn't surprises not broadcasting to the party it's
最小化实际上，有很多方法可以重新计算这是所有消息
minimization actually there are a lot of ways to recount all the messages this is
ways to recount all the messages this is actually in my case I did it similar to
实际上，就我而言，我所做的与我需要确定的顺序交易相似
actually in my case I did it similar to the sequential trade I needed to decide
the sequential trade I needed to decide how to accept all of the messages and I
如何接受所​​有信息，我需要真正决定形成方式
how to accept all of the messages and I needed to actually decide the formation
needed to actually decide the formation of the trade inside of this mark and in
标记内的交易，在我的情况下，我只是喜欢写下顶部
of the trade inside of this mark and in my case I just do love to write the top
my case I just do love to write the top bottom and my last part again when I
当我不能为所需的像素做颜色时，又是底部和最后一部分
bottom and my last part again when I can't do a color of the pixel I needed
can't do a color of the pixel I needed to maximize this message and in
为了最大程度地利用此消息，在计算中我也将其设置为
to maximize this message and in calculation I do also make them because
calculation I do also make them because these two are all written in turn we
这两个都是依次写的，我们不会找到最大化的
these two are all written in turn we won't find the maximized
我们想要的是在模拟社会中有更大的生存空间，而我有一个
and what we want is to have a larger be under simulate society and I have a
under simulate society and I have a weighting factors order from other
权重因子从保留中的其他消息和
weighting factors order from other messages from the reservation and from
messages from the reservation and from some neighbors for neighbors in this
在这种情况下，一些邻居对邻居表示敬意
some neighbors for neighbors in this case the respect eyes
我的意思是与传递消息相反的是单数是芒斯特
I mean the contrary to the message passing is the singular is the munster
passing is the singular is the munster of believe the publication this case the
认为出版物这种情况下我如何有一个复杂的方式不在这里
of believe the publication this case the way how I we have a complicated not here
way how I we have a complicated not here it's maybe more complicated than range
它可能比范围更复杂，但我们可以将其组合成很多
it's maybe more complicated than range but we can the composite into a lot of
but we can the composite into a lot of groups very simple tree then we
将非常简单的树分组，然后我们总结来自每个树的消息
groups very simple tree then we summarize the messages from each of
summarize the messages from each of trainees we get a total messages and
学员，我们获得了总体信息，效果很好，并且有很多
trainees we get a total messages and this works well well and there are a lot
this works well well and there are a lot of things we can design here first is
首先我们可以设计的是作曲家对所追踪的
of things we can design here first is how weighted the composer the traced and
how weighted the composer the traced and how a way to infiltrate this will be
如何渗透到这一点将非常有趣，在这种情况下，
how a way to infiltrate this will be very interesting and in this case in my
very interesting and in this case in my coding I got to this left to right and
编码我从左到右
我想从质量库中获取图像并
very interesting and in this case in my coding I got to this left to right and
with I want to images from the quality library and
我想从质量库中获取图像并
library and and the way I needed to close to turn
以及我需要关闭的方法来将它们变成彩色RPG变成黑白色
and the way I needed to close to turn these to a color RPG into a black white
these to a color RPG into a black white I just to use my bathroom like to try
我只是想用我的浴室来尝试应该达到的范围
I just to use my bathroom like to try the at which the range it should be
the at which the range it should be black this is after I am and which is
黑色，这是我之后的状态，里面仍然是黑色，是白色
black this is after I am and which is still the black inside is a white
still the black inside is a white surrounded by the whites then I energy
被白人包围，然后我的能量正在减少是无法坐下来的
surrounded by the whites then I energy is decreasing is no way to sit down the
is decreasing is no way to sit down the later I used here I can actually use
后来我用在这里我实际上可以使用不同的
later I used here I can actually use different
这是我随董事会发送的使用情况，这很好
this is the using I send along the board and this is mix good
在这里和这里丢卡文化不是很好，这就是
drop cards here and here the culture is not very good and this is the
not very good and this is the propagation to believe to be I this is
传播相信是我这是对所有事物尝试总结的眼睛
propagation to believe to be I this is the eyes to try summarize to all the be
the eyes to try summarize to all the be other images actually long as you stab
其他图像实际上只要您将其刺穿就可以转换，这就是消息
other images actually long as you stab it just convert this is the message
it just convert this is the message accounting I to make a trade
会计我做交易
因为我的编码仅对图像执行此操作，所以II只能拼写此代码
it just convert this is the message accounting I to make a trade
because of my coding is only doing this to images then I I just gotta spell this
因为我的编码仅对图像执行此操作，所以II只能拼写此代码
to images then I I just gotta spell this - he looks - fine then I I can also
-他看起来-很好，然后II也可以先放松一下
- he looks - fine then I I can also chill before well how do they do
假设我说如果我再选一张的话这好吃
suppose this tasty I said if I pick another image
这会导致标签或假设它对于ITN看起来也非常好
this leads to labels or suppose it's looked also very good for ITN
这是真的
this was true
太好了
wonderful Oh
在这种情况下，我是多球亲王，因为社交圈很大
in this case I am Prince multi-ball a good because socially big marzyong
good because socially big marzyong remove this part we we don't like the
删除这部分，我们不喜欢那些心相信的维持者
remove this part we we don't like the sustain those heart believes to
sustain those heart believes to constrain
约束
-比医疗补助更好
sustain those heart believes to constrain
- much better than Medicaid
还有先生到非部门的预告片的序列太乱了
and also mr. Messer the sequence to the trailer which is not a department is too
trailer which is not a department is too flexible
灵活的masterda假设查看这些参数
flexible masterda assume look at those parameters
masterda assume look at those parameters wait until the weight of each of three I
等到三个人的体重我在这里有两个，也要坚强
wait until the weight of each of three I have two here and also the way to strong
have two here and also the way to strong evidence and the weight from neighbors
证据和邻居的重量，我们可以调整那些，如果我杀了我
evidence and the weight from neighbors we can tune those and the if I kill me
we can tune those and the if I kill me too
也
并以一种方式
we can tune those and the if I kill me too
and in one way of
这可能是
this could be
我不知道这是否够糟糕，但听可以导致我们所有那些
I don't know whether this is bad enough but listen can lead to us all those that
but listen can lead to us all those that we can select a path parameter this
我们可以选择一个路径参数，这样可以使照片质量更高
we can select a path parameter this become a higher quality of photos to the
become a higher quality of photos to the picture mechanizations
图片机械化
因为如果我们走得太远
become a higher quality of photos to the picture mechanizations
because if we make it too far along
你知道这是事实，我们的最佳选择是整个
you know this is the truth our ultra spot please the whole part is to
spot please the whole part is to becoming the boat because i propagate
之所以成为船，是因为我串联后从左向右传播
becoming the boat because i propagate left to right I think after tandem
left to right I think after tandem dominant this trilogy is the final a
这部三部曲占主导地位，是我认为爱房子的最终王位密码
dominant this trilogy is the final a code of throne that love a house I think
code of throne that love a house I think they did a very good coding
他们做了很好的编码
感谢您的关注
code of throne that love a house I think they did a very good coding
of
感谢您的关注
thank you for your attention
[掌声]
[Applause]
是的
yeah
我不知道
I don't know